Finding Aid for University of Michigan Faculty and Staff Portraits ca. 1860-ca. 1960
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs
  - Nagele-Swinton
    - O'Neill, James Milton, 1881-1970. (Box 3)
    - Ormondroyd, Jesse, 1897- (Box 3)
    - O'Roke, Earl Cleveland, b. 1887. (Box 3)
    - Orr, Leslie W. (Box 3)
    - Osborne, Jay M. (Box 3)
    - Ottley, Jimmy. [postman] (Box 3)
    - Palmer, Alonzo Benjamin, 1815-1887. (Box 3)
    - Pargment, Lila D., b. 1888. (Box 3)
    - Pargment, Michael S. (Box 3)
    - Parker, DeWitt Henry, 1885-1949. (Box 3)
    - Parnall, Christopher Gregg. (Box 3)
    - Parsons, John Purl. (Box 3)
    - Partridge, Everett Percy, 1902-1969. (Box 3)
    - Paton, William Andrew, 1889- (Box 3)
    - Pattengill, Albert Henderson, 1842-1906. (Box 3)
    - Patterson, George Washington, 1799-1879. (Box 3)
    - Pawlowski, Felix Wladyslaw, b. 1876. (Box 3)
    - Pearson, Anthony A. (Box 3)
    - Peckham, Howard Henry, 1910- (Box 3)
    - Peirce, Carleton B. (Box 3)
    - Peterson, A. R. (Box 3)
    - Peterson, Frederick William, 1869- (Box 3)
    - Peterson, Reuben, 1862-1942. (Box 3)
    - Peterson, Shorey. (Box 3)
    - Pettee, William Henry, 1838-1904. (Box 3)
    - Phelps, Dudley Maynard. (Box 3)
    - Pick, Hanns. (Box 3)
    - Pillsbury, Walter Bowers, 1872-1960. (Box 3)
    - Plumer, James M., 1899-1960. (Box 3)
    - Pollard, H. Marvin. (Box 3)
    - Pollock, James Barkley, 1863-1934. (Box 3)
    - Poor, Vincent Collins. (Box 3)
    - Potter, Eugene Breckenridge, 1899- (Box 3)
    - Prescott, Albert Benjamin, 1832-1905. (Box 3)
    - Preuss, Lawrence, 1905-1956. (Box 3)
    - Price, Hereward Thimbleby, 1880-1964. (Box 3)
    - Price, Percival, 1901- (Box 3)
    - Purdom, Thomas Luther. (Box 3)
    - Radock, Michael, 1917- (Box 3)
    - Raiford, Theodore Ernest, b. 1889. (Box 3)
    - Ramsdell, Willett Forrest, 1890-1951. (Box 3)
    - Randall, Harrison M. (Harrison McAllister), 1870-1969. (Box 3)
    - Ransom, Henry King, 1898-1983. (Box 3)
    - Rebec, George, 1868-1944. (Box 3)
    - Reed, John Oren, 1856-1916. (Box 3)
    - Reeves, Jesse Siddall, 1872-1942. (Box 3)
    - Reichart, Walter Albert, 1903- (Box 3)
    - Reighard, Jacob Ellsworth, 1861-1942. (Box 3)
    - Remer, Charles F. (Box 3)
    - Rice, Warner Grenelle, 1899- (Box 3)
    - Rich, Daniel Leslie, b. 1879. (Box 3)
    - Rickert, Ura Garfield. (Box 3)
    - Rickett, Reginald L. (Box 3)
    - Riecker, Herman H. (Box 4)
    - Riegel, John W. (Box 4)
    - Riggs, Henry Earle, 1865-1949. (Box 4)
    - Riven, Samuel S. (Box 4)
    - Robbins, Frank Egleston, 1884-1963. (Box 4)
    - Robinson, Stillman Williams, 1838-1910. (Box 4)
    - Rodkey, Robert Gordon, b. 1885. (Box 4)
    - Rogers, Henry Wade, 1853-1926. (Box 4)
    - Rogers, James Speed, 1891-1955. (Box 4)
    - Rolfe, John Carew, 1859-1943. (Box 4)
    - Rood, John R. (John Romain), b. 1868. (Box 4)
    - Rose, Preston Benjamin, 1834-1912. (Box 4)
    - Ross, George G. (Box 4)
    - Ross, Gilbert, 1903- (Box 4)
    - Roth, Filibert, 1858-1925. (Box 4)
    - Rovillain, Eugène Etienne. (Box 4)
    - Rowe, Kenneth Thorpe, 1900- (Box 4)
    - Rufus, Will Carl, 1876-1946. (Box 4)
    - Rugen, Mabel E. (Box 4)
    - Running, Theodore R. (Theodore Rudolph), b. 1866. (Box 4)
    - Russell, Israel Cook, 1852-1906. (Box 4)
    - Sacks, Jacob, 1901- (Box 4)
    - Sadler, Herbert Charles, 1872-1948. (Box 4)
    - Sadler, Walter C. (Box 4)
    - Sage, F. L. (Box 4)
    - Sager, Abram, 1810-1877. (Box 4)
    - Sanders, Henry Arthur, 1868-1956. (Box 4)
    - Sawyer, Ralph A. (Ralph Alanson), 1895-1978. (Box 4)
    - Schenk, Philip Louis. (Box 4)
    - Schlotterbeck, Julius Otto, 1865-1917. (Box 4)
    - Schneider, Francis Lee. (Box 4)
    - Schneidewind, Richard. (Box 4)
    - Schoepfle, Chester Seitz, 1892- (Box 4)
    - Scholl, John William, b. 1869. (Box 4)
    - Schorling, Raleigh, 1887-1950. (Box 4)
    - Scott, Frank. (Box 4)
    - Scott, Fred Newton, 1860-1931. (Box 4)
    - Scott, Irving Day, 1877-1955. (Box 4)
    - Senstius, Maurice William, b. 1888. (Box 4)
    - Severance, Henry O. (Henry Ormal), 1867- (Box 4)
    - Sewall, Henry, 1855-1936. (Box 4)
    - Sharman, Jackson Roger, 1895-1957. (Box 4)
    - Shartel, Burke Woods, 1889-1967. (Box 4)
    - Sherlock, Robert H. (Box 4)
    - Shull, Aaron Franklin, 1881-1961. (Box 4)
    - Simes, Lewis M. (Lewis Mallalieu), b. 1889. (Box 4)
    - Sink, Charles Albert, 1879-1972. (Box 4)
    - Sleator, William Warner, 1883-1956. (Box 4)
    - Slocum, George, 1865-1933. (Box 4)
    - Slosson, Preston William, 1892- (Box 4)
    - Smeaton, William Gabb. (Box 4)
    - Smith, Allan Frederick, 1911- (Box 4)
    - Smith, Arthur Whitmore, 1874- (Box 4)
    - Smith, Dean Tyler. (Box 4)
    - Smith, Ralph G., 1920- (Box 4)
    - Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959. (Box 4)
    - Sommer, Ralph F. (Box 4)
    - Soule, Harrison, 1832-1922. (Box 4)
    - Soule, Malcolm H. (Box 4)
    - Spalding, Volney Morgan, 1849-1918. (Box 4)
    - Spence, Adam Knight, 1831-1900. (Box 4)
    - Spooner, Charles W. (Box 4)
    - Stahl, Otto J. (Box 4)
    - Stanley, Albert Augustus, 1851-1932. (Box 4)
    - Stason, E. Blythe (Edwin Blythe), 1891-1972. (Box 4)
    - Steere, Joseph B. (Joseph Beale), 1842-1940. (Box 4)
    - Steere, William Campbell, 1907- (Box 4)
    - Stephenson, Orlando Worth. (Box 4)
    - Stevens, Albert K. (Box 4)
    - Stevens, Alviso Burdett, b. 1853. (Box 4)
    - Stocking, Charles Howard, 1882-1958. (Box 4)
    - Stoodley, Agnes L. (Box 4)
    - Stout, Melville Bigham, 1895- (Box 4)
    - Stowell, C. H. (Charles Henry), b. 1850. (Box 4)
    - Streeter, George Linius, 1873-1948. (Box 4)
    - Stuart, Duane Reed. (Box 4)
    - Sullivan, Eugene Cornelius, b. 1872. (Box 4)
    - Sunderland, Edson Read, 1874-1959. (Box 4)
    - Swan, Henry Harrison, 1840-1916. (Box 4)
    - Swinton, Roy Stanley, d. 1956. (Box 4)
  - Taft-Zuck
    - Taft, Jonathan, 1820-1903. (Box 4)
    - Talamon, René L. (Box 4)
    - Tappan, Henry Philip, 1805-1881. (Box 4)
    - Tappan, John L. (Box 4)
    - Tatlock, John Strong Perry, 1876-1948. (Box 4)
    - Taylor, Clarence George. (Box 4)
    - Taylor, F. M. (Fred Manville), 1855-1932. (Box 4)
    - Taylor, William Randolph, 1895- (Box 4)
    - Tealdi, Aubrey. (Box 4)
    - Ten Broook, Andrew, 1814-1899. (Box 4)
    - Thieme, Hugo Paul, 1870-1940. (Box 4)
    - Thomas, Calvin, 1854-1919. (Box 4)
    - Thomassen, Lars, 1896- (Box 4)
    - Thompson, Bradley Martin, 1835-1917. (Box 4)
    - Thompson, Elizabeth Lockwood. (Box 4)
    - Thornton, Jesse E. (Jesse Earl) (Box 4)
    - Thorpe, Clarence D. (Clarence DeWitt), 1887-1959. (Box 4)
    - Tilden, Charles Joseph, b. 1873. (Box 4)
    - Tilley, Morris Palmer, 1876-1947. (Box 4)
    - Timoshenko, Stephen, 1878-1972. (Box 4)
    - Timoshenko, V. P., b. 1885. (Box 4)
    - Titiev, Mischa, 1901- (Box 4)
    - Titus, Helen M. (Box 4)
    - Toro, Julio del, 1887- (Box 4)
    - Tracy, John Evarts, 1880-1959. (Box 4)
    - Trowbridge, P. F. (Perry Fox), 1866-1937. (Box 4)
    - Trueblood, Thomas Clarkson, 1856-1951. (Box 4)
    - Trytten, John M. (Box 4)
    - Tyler, Moses Coit, 1835-1900. (Box 4)
    - Upthegrove, Clair. (Box 4)
    - Van den Broek, John Abraham, 1885-1959. (Box 4)
    - Van Deursen, Hardin A. (Box 4)
    - Van Zwaluwenburg, James Gerrit, 1874-1922. (Box 4)
    - Vaughan, Henry Frieze, 1889-1979. (Box 4)
    - Vaughan, Victor C. (Victor Clarence), 1851-1929. (Box 4)
    - Vedder, Francis Bulkley. (Box 4)
    - Wade, James Henry, 1834-1924. (Box 4)
    - Waggoner, Raymond W. (Raymond Walter), 1901- (Box 4)
    - Wagner, Charles Philip, b. 1876. (Box 4)
    - Wagner, Frank Caspar, 1864-1928. (Box 4)
    - Wagner, Herbert P. (Box 4)
    - Wahr, Frederick B. (Frederick Burkhart), b. 1889. (Box 4)
    - Wait, William H. (William Henry) (Box 4)
    - Waite, Herbert Harold. (Box 4)
    - Waite, John Barker, 1882- (Box 4)
    - Walker, Charles Irish, 1814-1895. (Box 4)
    - Wallner, Julius M. (Box 4)
    - Walter, Edward Lorraine. (Box 4)
    - Walton, Ivan. (Box 4)
    - Ward, Marcus Llewellyn, 1875-1963. (Box 4)
    - Warthin, Aldred Scott, 1866-1931. (Box 4)
    - Waterman, Leroy, 1875-1972. (Box 4)
    - Waterman, Merwin H. (Merwin Howe), 1903- (Box 4)
    - Watkins, Herbert Gale, 1889-1967. (Box 4)
    - Watkins, Leonard Lyon, 1896- (Box 4)
    - Watson, James Craig, 1838-1880. (Box 4)
    - Wead, Charles Kasson, 1848-1925. (Box 4)
    - Wead, Mary Eunice. (Box 4)
    - Weaver, Bennet, 1892-1970. (Box 4)
    - Webster, Randolph W. (Box 4)
    - Welch, Paul Smith, b. 1882. (Box 4)
    - Weller, Carl Vernon, 1887-1956. (Box 4)
    - Wells, William Palmer, 1831-1891. (Box 4)
    - Wenger, Christian N. (Box 4)
    - Wenley, Robert M. (Robert Mark), 1861-1929. (Box 4)
    - Wenrich, Ralph C. (Box 4)
    - Whedon, D. D. (Daniel Denison), 1808-1885. (Box 4)
    - Wheeler, Benjamin W. (Box 4)
    - Whipple, Guy Montrose, 1876-1941. (Box 4)
    - White, Albert Easton, 1884-1956. (Box 4)
    - White, Andrew Dickson, 1832-1918. (Box 4)
    - White, Lee A., 1886-1971. (Box 4)
    - Whitney, Allen Sisson, 1857-1944. (Box 4)
    - Wight, Howard Marshall, b. 1889. (Box 4)
    - Wilder, Raymond Louis, 1896- (Box 4)
    - Wile, Udo Julius, b. 1882. (Box 4)
    - Wilford, Bill H. (Box 4)
    - Wilgus, Horace LaFayette, 1859-1935. (Box 4)
    - Willard, Hobart Hurd, 1881-1974. (Box 4)
    - Willey, Norman Leroy. (Box 4)
    - Williams, George Palmer, 1802-1881. (Box 4)
    - Williams, Mentor Lee, 1901-1956. (Box 4)
    - Williams, Neil Hooker, 1870-1956. (Box 4)
    - Williams, Robley C. (Box 4)
    - Williamson, Edward Bruce, 1877-1933. (Box 4)
    - Wilson, Clyde Elmore. (Box 4)
    - Wilson, Frank Norman, 1890-1952. (Box 4)
    - Wilson, Thomas Pardon, d. 1909. (Box 4)
    - Winchell, Alexander, 1824-1891. (Box 4)
    - Winkler, Max, 1866-1930. (Box 4)
    - Winter, John Garrett, 1881-1956. (Box 4)
    - Winters, Robert K. (Box 4)
    - Wisler, Chester Owen, 1881- (Box 4)
    - Wood, Arthur Evans, b. 1881. (Box 4)
    - Wood, De Volson, 1832-1897. (Box 4)
    - Wood, James Craven, 1858-1948. (Box 4)
    - Wood, H. James. (Box 4)
    - Wood, Norman Asa, 1857-1943. (Box 4)
    - Wood, William P. (William Platt), 1888- (Box 4)
    - Woody, Clifford, 1884-1948. (Box 4)
    - Worley, John Stephen, b. 1876. (Box 4)
    - Worrell, William Hoyt, b. 1879. (Box 4)
    - Wrentmore, Clarence George, 1867-1919. (Box 4)
    - Yaeger, Edgar. (Box 4)
    - Yeatter, Ralph Emerson, 1896- (Box 4)
    - Yntema, Hessel Edward, 1891-1966. (Box 4)
    - Yoakum, Clarence Stone, 1879-1945. (Box 4)
    - Yost, Fielding Harris, 1871-1946. (Box 4)
    - Young, Edward. (Box 4)
    - Young, Leigh Jarvis, 1883-1960. (Box 4)
    - Yutzy, Simon Menno. (Box 4)
    - Zacharias, Allen Howard. (Box 4)
    - Ziwet, Alexander, 1853-1928. (Box 4)
    - Zuck, Harry E. (Box 4)
  - Group Portraits
    - Literary faculty of 1867, 1880 (Box 4)